Guide to the Director of Athletics Records, 1939-2007, bulk 1968-2007 UA.13.01.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files (UA86-7), 1977-1984, 2.5 boxes
  - Facilities
    - Football Stadium, paving of concourse, 1982 July-Aug. (Box 13)
    - Lacrosse field, 1982 (Box 13)
    - Soccer field, 1983 (Box 13)
  - Information on Cameron preservation, 1981-1982 (Box 13)
  - Information on Coaches, 1982 Dec. (Box 13)
  - Information on naming building (Dr. Powell), 1982 (Box 13)
  - Information on press box facility, 1981-1982 (Box 13)
  - NCAA meeting [St. Louis, MO.], 1981 Dec. (Box 13)
  - NCAA meeting [Houston, TX], 1982 Jan. (Box 13)
  - NCAA news, 1982-1983, 2 folders (Box 13)
  - NCAA [Vacendak's information], 1981-1982 (Box 15)
  - Personal [other], 1980-1982 (Box 15)
  - Raycom, 1982 (Box 15)
  - Sports
    - Fencing, 1982 (Box 15)
    - Lacrosse, 1981 (Box 15)
    - Soccer, 1982-1983 (Box 15)
    - Swimming [information Re:eliminating], 1982 (Box 15)
    - Tennis, 1982 (Box 15)
    - Tennis-women, 1983-1984 (Box 15)
    - Track, 1982-1983 (Box 15)
    - Wrestling, 1982 (Box 15)
  - Staff correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - Surveys, 1982-1983 (Box 15)
  - TV rights, 1982 (Box 15)
  - Title IX, 1978 Nov.-1980, 4 folders (Box 15)
  - Steve Vacendek's
    - ACC correspondence, 1982 (Box 15)
    - Basketball and baseball, 1982 (Box 15)
    - College Football Association, 1980-1982 (Box 15)
    - Football, 1980-1982 (Box 15)
- Subject Files (UA86-53/UA89-48), 1978-1985, 3 boxes
  Accession contains correspondence and memoranda, reports, sports files, and scholarship athletes material. Sports files contain eligibility lists, rosters, statistics, contest reports, and player statements. Scholarship athlete material includes men's and women's sports, consisting of correspondence and memoranda concerning scholarship renewal and terms and conditions of acceptance. NCAA and ACC material is also present. Accession UA89-48 is at the end of box 17.
  - Sports (Box 16)
    - Baseball, 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Basketball, 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Cross-Country, 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Fencing, 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Football, 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Golf, 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Lacrosse, 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Soccer, 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Swimming, 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Tennis, 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Indoor Track, 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Outdoor Track, 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 16)
    - Wrestling, 1979-1982, 3 folders (Box 16)
  - Scholarship Athletes [men's sports]
    - Football
      - Armstrong, Mike, 1978-1981 (Box 16)
      - Bacon, Paul, 1978-1981 (Box 16)
      - Baldinger, Brain, 1978-1981 (Box 16)
      - Bamberger, Greg, 1978-1981 (Box 16)
      - Bellan, Larry, 1982-1983 (Box 16)
      - Bowser, Charles, 1978-1981 (Box 16)
      - Brinkman, John, 1978-1981 (Box 16)
      - Brower, Bobby, 1978-1981 (Box 16)
      - Brown, Craig, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
      - Brown, Edward P., 1978-1981 (Box 16)
      - Brown, Marvin L., 1978-1980 (Box 16)
      - Browning, Chandler Craig, 1978-1981 (Box 16)
      - Brummitt, Richard, 1978-1981 (Box 16)
      - Cerone, James R., 1980-1981 (Box 16)
      - Churm, Michael, 1978-1981 (Box 16)
      - Colantuoni, James A., 1978-1981 (Box 16)
      - Collins, William, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
      - Crenshaw, Keith, 1979-1981 (Box 16)
      - Dowell, Dwayne, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Eisenberg, Judd, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Fredrick, Ron, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
      - Fuqua, Michael G., 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Garstkiewicz, Gary, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Harper, Tracy, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Heinsohn, Paul, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Jenkins, Robert, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Jones, Cedric, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Lenoir, Larry, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Long, James, 1982-1983 (Box 17)
      - Mancini, Anthony, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Martin, Fletcher, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - McIver, James, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - McKinney, Scott, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Pacitti, David C., 1984-1985 (Box 17)
      - Patterson, Robert B., 1979-1980 (Box 17)
      - Pelosky, Robert J., 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Rhinesmith, Michael, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
      - Price, Zac, 1978-1982 (Box 17)
      - Rowe, Joseph C., 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Ryan, Micheal, 1979-1980 (Box 17)
      - Schoettmer, Mark, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Snow, David, 1979-1982 (Box 17)
      - Spiers, John, 1982-1983 (Box 17)
      - Stopper, Michael, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Tabron, Dennis, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
      - Thielemann, Dave, 1978-1980 (Box 17)
      - Tyson, Jimmy, 1978-1982 (Box 17)
      - Welsh, Dan, 1978-1982 (Box 17)
      - Yellott, Dan, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
    - Basketball
      - Banks, Eugene, 1977-1980 (Box 17)
      - Dennard, Kenneth, 1977-1981 (Box 17)
      - Jackman, Bill, 1982-1983 (Box 17)
      - Suddath, James E. 1977-1981 (Box 17)
      - Taylor, Vince, 1978-1982 (Box 17)
      - Wendt, Greg, 1982-1983 (Box 17)
      - Williams, Allen, 1979-1983 (Box 17)
    - Baseball
      - Brassill, Tom, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
      - Nolan, Ed, 1979 (Box 17)
      - Pruett, Don, 1979-1981 (Box 17)
      - Rigby, Kevin, 1979 (Box 17)
    - Golf
      - Goettman, Jeffrey, 1977-1981 (Box 17)
      - Ryan, John, 1980-1982 (Box 17)
    - Lacrosse
      - Hagler, Dave, 1978-1982 (Box 17)
      - Megale, Joseph, 1977-1980 (Box 17)
    - Soccer, Farran, Thomas, 1981-1982 (Box 17)
    - Track, McCallister, Mark, 1978-1981 (Box 17)
    - Wrestling, Nadzak, Walter, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - Scholarship Athletes [women's sports]
    - Basketball, McCarthy, Tara, 1977-1981 (Box 17)
    - Golf, Rogan, Susan, 1980-1981 (Box 17)
  - ACC correspondence, 1972 Dec.-1983 (Box 17)
  - ACC meeting [Myrtle Beach, SC], 1983 May (Box 17)
  - ACC spring meeting [Myrtle Beach, SC], 1984 May (Box 17)
  - Business operations [Paul Detomo], 1973-1975 (Box 17)
  - College Football Association (CFA), 1983 (Box 17)
  - Equipment room, 1982-1983 (Box 17)
  - Carl James [associate director], 1969-1976 (Box 17)
  - NCAA
    - 1972 July-1976 (Box 17)
    - 1977-1979 June (Box 17)
    - Correspondence, 1983 Jan.-1985 March, 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Meeting, Jan. 1982 [San Diego, CA], 1981 Nov.-1982 Jan. (Box 17)
  - CFA, 1978 (Box 17)
  - National Association of Collegiate Directors of Athletics-proceedings, 1978 (Box 17)
  - Raycom, 1983 (Box 17)
  - Report, [1972?] (Box 17)
- Subject Files (UA90-3), 1982-1985, 1.5 boxes
  Accession contains correspondence, recommendations, minutes, budget material, and material pertaining to the maintenance and improvement of various athletic facilities. Prominent subjects include Athletic Council, ACC, College Football Association, and NCAA.
  Conditions Governing Access note
  For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the director of the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist. Please consult reference archivist in to determine which materials are effected by the restriction.
  - Athletic Council, 1985 Aug.-Nov. (Box 18)
  - Athletic Council meeting, 1985 Dec. (Box 18)
  - Athletic Council, William Bradford [chair], 1983 June-1985, 2 folders (Box 18)
  - ACC
    - 1983-1984 (Box 18)
    - Meeting [Myrtle Beach, SC], 1985 May (Box 18)
    - Meeting [Greensboro, NC], 1985 Dec. (Box 18)
    - ACC workshop [Greensboro, NC], 1985 May (Box 18)
    - Women's Basketball Tournament, 1985 (Box 18)
  - Basketball bulletins, 1984-1985 (Box 18)
  - Facilities
    - Athletic Facility (proposed), 1983-1985 (Box 18)
    - Coombs Field, 1982-1984 (Box 18)
    - Finch-Yeager building, 1983 (Box 18)
    - Football building (proposed), 1984-1985 (Box 18)
    - Health, Physical Education, and Recreation Athletics Sports Medicine, 1984 Jan.-Feb. (Box 18)
    - Indoor tennis, 1983 Oct.-1984 Feb (Box 18)
    - Information on renovations, Cameron/Half Time House, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Miscellaneous improvements, 1982-1985 (Box 18)
    - Information on lighting, 1981-1983 (Box 18)
    - Wallace Wade Stadium, lighting, 1982-1984 (Box 18)
  - Children's Classic (Jerry Neville), 1982-1985 (Box 18)
  - College Football Association
    - 1984 (Box 18)
    - Board of Directors correspondence, 1984 (Box 18)
    - Meeting [Dallas, TX], 1984 April-July (Box 18)
    - Board of Directors meeting [New Orleans, LA], 1985 July-Oct. (Box 18)
    - Board of Directors, 1985 (Box 18)
    - 1985, 3 folders (Box 18)
    - Ad-Hoc Committee on College Football Television, 1983-1984 (Box 18)
  - Steve Sloan (correspondence received), 1982 (Box 18)
  - Correspondence, budget, 1983-1985 (Box 18)
  - Letters of recommendation, 1982-1985 (Box 18)
  - Charles B. Heustis, 1982-1984 (Box 18)
  - Dr. H. Keith H. Brodie's staff meeting, 1985 (Box 19)
  - Dr. Brodie, 1982-1985 (Box 19)
  - Kenneth Pye, 1983-1985 (Box 19)
  - Terry Sanford, 1983-1985, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Hall of Fame, 1985 April (Box 19)
  - IRS ruling, 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - Iron Dukes, 1985 (Box 19)
  - LIFE, 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - NCAA
    - Annual Convention [Dallas, TX], 1983 Sept.-1984 Jan. (Box 19)
    - Meeting [Chicago, IL], 1984 June (Box 19)
    - Special Convention [New Orleans, LA], 1985 May-June (Box 19)
    - 1985 (Box 19)
- Subject Files (UA94-106/2001-44), 1939-1999 (bulk 1983-1991), 7 boxes
  Accession contains correspondence and memoranda, reports, proposals, surveys, committee records, and budget material. Records pertain to various NCAA and ACC meetings, committees, and tournaments; Alumni affairs, the Athletic Council, television agreements, Iron Dukes, and facilities projects. Accession 2001-44, located in box 26, contains photocopies of 1939-1940 correspondence between Wallace Wade and Duke Football player, Charles Hipp.
  Also present in this series are records of the Board of Trustees. Records of the University's Board of Trustees which have been in existence for at least fifty years are available for scholarly research with the permission of the University Archivist. Access to records which have been in existence for less than fifty years shall be granted only by special permission, in writing, from the Board of Trustees.
  - ACC
    - 1986 (Box 19)
    - Letters of intent, 1986 (Box 19)
    - ACC basketball bulletins, 1986-1987, 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Meetings, 1986 March-April (Box 19)
    - [general], 1986 (Box 19)
    - ACC Meeting [Myrtle Beach, SC], 1986 March-May (Box 19)
  - Agent Information, 1985-1986, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Admissions, 1986 (Box 19)
  - Audits, 1986 (Box 19)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1983-1986 (Box 19)
  - Athletic Council, 1985 Dec.-1986 (Box 19)
  - Athletic Council meeting, 1986 Dec. (Box 19)
  - Athletic Council Report for 1985-1986 (Box 19)
  - Banquets, 1984-1985 (Box 19)
  - Board of Trustees, 1985-1986 (Box 19)
  - Journal vouchers, 1986 (Box 19)
  - Campaign for Arts and Sciences, 1984-1986 (Box 19)
  - Children's Classic, 1986 (Box 19)
  - Clemson's NCAA situation, correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 19)
  - Correspondence [budget], 1986-1987 Jan. (Box 19)
  - College Football Association, 1986, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - Questionnaires, 1982-1986 (Box 20)
  - Revenue management plan, 1988 (Box 20)
  - National Association of College Directors of Athletics, 1988 (Box 20)
  - NCAA
    - Legislation, 1986 (Box 20)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 20)
    - President's Commission National Forum [Orlando, FL.], 1988 June (Box 20)
    - Convention [Nashville, TN], 1987 Oct.-1988 Jan. (Box 20)
    - Division I Basketball Committee, 1987-1988 (Box 20)
    - Division I Basketball Committee meeting [Dallas, TX], 1988 June-Aug. (Box 20)
    - Division IA Television Committee [football], 1988, 4 folders (Box 20)
    - Division IA Television Committee meeting [Chicago, IL], 1988 May-Sept. (Box 20)
    - Division IA Television Committee, 1988 Jan.-Feb. (Box 20)
    - Television Committee meeting [Kansan City, MO], 1988 April (Box 20)
    - Questionnaires, 1987-1988 (Box 20)
  - Management Board meeting, 1988 August 11 (Box 20)
  - Miscellaneous [Management Board], 1988 (Box 20)
  - E.J. McDonald's staff meeting, 1988 Aug.-Nov. (Box 20)
  - 5th year eligibilities, 1984-1988 (Box 20)
  - Raycom, 1987 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Amateur Sports, 1986 (Box 20)
  - North Carolina Amateur Sports, Board of Directors meeting, 1986 Dec. (Box 20)
  - ACC
    - 1987 (Box 20)
    - ACC Tournament [Landover, MD], 1987 March (Box 20)
    - May meeting [Myrtle Beach, SC], 1987 March-May 1987 (Box 20)
    - April workshop, 1987 (Box 20)
  - Agents, 1987 (Box 20)
  - Athletic Council meeting, 1987 April (Box 20)
  - Admissions, 1987 (Box 20)
  - CFA meeting [Dallas, TX], 1986 May-June (Box 21)
  - Board of Directors [CFA], 1986 (Box 21)
  - Complimentary ticket lists, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Conflict of interest letters, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
  - Television agreements
    - Jefferson-Pilot football television contract, 1984-1985 (Box 21)
    - CBS, 1982-1983 (Box 21)
    - NBC, 1981-1982 (Box 21)
    - ABC, 1981-1983 (Box 21)
    - Raycom, 1982-1984 (Box 21)
    - Other television agreements/contracts, 1983-1987 (Box 21)
  - Dataflow contract, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Cameron, expanding seating, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Home Team Sports (HTS), soccer, 1985 (Box 21)
  - Adcock, Jack, 1985-86 (Box 21)
  - Dr. Brodie, 1985-1986 (Box 21)
  - E.J. McDonald, 1986 (Box 21)
  - A. Kenneth Pye, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous, 1983-1986 (Box 21)
  - Development Office, 1983-1986 (Box 21)
  - Drug Education and Awareness Program, 1985-1986 (Box 21)
  - Hall of Fame, 1982-1985 (Box 21)
  - Health, Phys. Ed., and Recreation/DUAA, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Grounds information, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Skybox, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Insurance, 1982-1986 (Box 21)
  - New football building [weight room, training room, equipment room], 1986 (Box 21)
  - Iron Dukes, 1986, 2 folders (Box 21)
  - Safrit, R.W., 1986 (Box 21)
  - Trips, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Miscellaneous, 1985 Dec.-1986, 3 folders (Box 21)
  - NCAA, 1986 (Box 21)
  - NCAA Division I Directors meeting [Chicago, IL], 1986 June-Aug. (Box 21)
  - Athletic Council, 1987 (Box 22)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1987 Feb.-April (Box 22)
  - Board of Trustees, 1987 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence [budget], 1987 (Box 22)
  - CFA, 1987, 2 folders (Box 22)
  - CFA meeting [Dallas Hyatt Regency], 1987 May (Box 22)
  - Dr. Brodie, 1987 (Box 22)
  - Mr. McDonald, 1987 (Box 22)
  - Mr. Pye, 1987 (Box 22)
  - Mr. A.E. Finley, 1984-1987 (Box 22)
  - Hall of Fame, 1986-1987 (Box 22)
  - Hall of Fame inductees, 1987 (Box 22)
  - Iron Duke correspondence, 1987 (Box 22)
  - Miscellaneous, 1987 (Box 22)
  - Tax rulings, 1986-1987 (Box 22)
  - NACDA, 1987 (Box 22)
  - NACDA meeting, 1987 October (Box 22)
  - NCAA, 1987 (Box 22)
  - NCAA conventions, 1987 (Box 22)
  - Club development interests (Advisory Board for University Clubs), 1987 (Box 22)
  - Administrative Services Management Board, 1986-1987 (Box 22)
  - Sports Festival, 1987 (Box 22)
  - Baseball, 1985-1986 (Box 22)
  - Basketball, 1986 (Box 22)
  - Club sports, 1985-1986 (Box 22)
  - Football coaching change, 1986-1987 (Box 22)
  - Student behavior, 1983-1984 (Box 22)
  - Summer camps, 1982-1986 (Box 22)
  - Television rights, 1983-1986 (Box 22)
  - Correspondence regarding ticket office, 1981-1986 (Box 22)
  - Title IX, 1982-1986 (Box 22)
  - ACC
    - 1988 (Box 22)
    - Spring meeting [Myrtle Beach, SC], 1988 April-June (Box 22)
    - Legislative proposals, 1987 (Box 22)
    - Citrus Bowl, 1988 (Box 22)
    - Corporate sponsorship, 1988 (Box 22)
    - Meeting [Naples], 1988 Feb. (Box 22)
    - Meeting [Airport Marriott], 1988 April (Box 22)
    - Meeting [Governor's Inn], 1988 Sept. (Box 22)
    - Faculty representatives and Athletic Directors meeting [Greensboro-High-Point Marriott], 1988 Oct. (Box 22)
    - Meeting [Greensboro-High-Point], 1988 (Box 23)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Athletic Council Meeting, 1987-1988 (Box 23)
  - Athletic Council correspondence, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Board of Trustees, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Campaign for Arts and Sciences, 1987-1988 (Box 23)
  - CFA
    - 1988 (Box 23)
    - Championship Committee meeting [Atlanta, GA], 1988 Aug.-Nov. (Box 23)
    - Football Championship game, 1987-1988 (Box 23)
  - Admissions, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Parking and Traffic Task Force report, 1988 Aug. (Box 23)
  - Dr. Brodie, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Mr. McDonald, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Development Office, 1987-1988 (Box 23)
  - Drug Program, 1987-1988 (Box 23)
  - Facilities
    - Hotel Project/golf course, 1987-1988 (Box 23)
    - Cameron Stadium scoreboard, 1988 (Box 23)
    - Improvements, 1987 (Box 23)
    - Cameron Indoor Stadium, 1987-1988, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Press Box, 1988 Aug. (Box 23)
    - Grounds, 1988 (Box 23)
    - Golf Course, 1988 (Box 23)
    - Iron Dukes, 1988 (Box 23)
    - Correspondence on fundraising for Cameron renovations, 1987-1988 (Box 23)
    - Golf course game plan, etc., 1988-1989 (Box 23)
    - Track, 1986-1987 (Box 23)
    - Recreational facility, 1986 October (Box 23)
    - I.M. Building, 1986-1987 (Box 23)
    - Baseball, 1986-1987 (Box 23)
    - EC Racquetball, 1987 (Box 23)
    - Tennis improvements, 1987 (Box 23)
    - William M. Weber, 1988 (Box 23)
  - Individual prospects clearance report, 1988 Feb. (Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous, 1988, 3 folders (Box 23)
  - National Invitation Tournament (NIT), 1982-1986 (Box 23)
  - National Football Foundation and Hall of Fame, 1984-1986 (Box 23)
  - Steve Sloan, 1983-1986 (Box 23)
  - Football contract letter, 1982 Dec. (Box 23)
  - North Carolina Amateur Sports, 1983-1985 (Box 24)
  - ACC
    - 1989 (Box 24)
    - Meeting [Orlando, FL], 1989 Jan.-Feb. (Box 24)
    - Meeting [Greensboro, NC], 1989 March-April (Box 24)
    - Meeting [Greensboro, NC], 1989 Sept-Dec., 3 folders (Box 24)
  - Admissions, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Correspondence, Athletic Council, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Audits, 1987-1989 (Box 24)
  - Budget correspondence, 1989 (Box 24)
  - CFA, 1989 (Box 24)
  - CFA Football Championship Meeting, 1989 Jan.-May (Box 24)
  - H. Keith H. Brodie, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Gene McDonald, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Development Office, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Improvements, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Golf Course, 1988-1989 (Box 24)
  - Iron Dukes, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Cameron, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Grounds, 1989 (Box 24)
  - Miscellaneous, 1989, 2 folders (Box 24)
  - NCAA
    - Division I, Television Committee [football], 1989 (Box 24)
    - Division I Basketball Committee, 1989 (Box 24)
    - Special Television Negotiations Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 24)
    - Restructuring Committee, 1988-1989 May (Box 24)
    - Restructuring Committee, 1989 Oct.-Dec. (Box 24)
    - Division I Men's Basketball Championship Press Conference, 1989 March 7 (Box 24)
    - Television Negotiating Committee Meeting [Chicago, IL], 1989 October (Box 24)
    - Convention, 1989 (Box 24)
    - NCAA, 1989 (Box 25)
  - NACDA, 1989 (Box 25)
  - Management Board, 1989 (Box 25)
  - McDonald's staff meetings, 1989 (Box 25)
  - Treyburn, 1988-1989 (Box 25)
  - University Club, 1989 (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 25)
  - Surveys, 1987 (Box 25)
  - Sports
    - Baseball, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Basketball, 1987-1989 (Box 25)
    - Football
      - 1988 (Box 25)
      - Correspondence [re: Spurrier], 1989 (Box 25)
      - 1989 (Box 25)
    - Soccer, 1987-1988 (Box 25)
  - ACC
    - ACC, 1990, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - ACC/Big East, 1988 Oct. (Box 25)
    - Big East [NY], 1989 Jan. 19 (Box 25)
    - Florida State University, 1988-1990 (Box 25)
    - Cost reduction, 1990 (Box 25)
    - Meeting [Marco Island, FL], 1990 Jan. (Box 25)
    - TV Committee meeting [Greensboro, NC], 1990 March (Box 25)
    - Meeting [Washington Duke Inn], 1990 April (Box 25)
    - Meeting [Myrtle Beach, SC], 1990 April-May (Box 25)
    - Miscellaneous [ACC], 1990 (Box 25)
    - Meeting [Greensboro, NC], 1990 July (Box 25)
    - Meeting, 1990 Oct. (Box 25)
    - Meeting [Greensboro, NC], 1990 Dec. (Box 25)
  - Alumni Affairs, 1990 (Box 25)
  - Terry Sanford/American Dance Festival, 1989 (Box 25)
  - Athletic Council, 1990 (Box 25)
  - Basketball scheduling information, 1990-1991 (Box 25)
  - Budget correspondence, 1990 (Box 25)
  - IR's purchase requisition, 1990 (Box 25)
  - Coach Murray correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 25)
  - Cameron-Wade Foundation, 1986-1989 (Box 25)
  - CFA, 1990 (Box 25)
  - Dr. Brodie, 1990 (Box 25)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 25)
  - Mr. McDonald, 1990 (Box 25)
  - Development, 1990 (Box 26)
  - Hall of Fame, 1988-1990, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - Aquatic Center, 1988 (Box 26)
  - Cameron bust, 1989 (Box 26)
  - Murray Building, 1989 (Box 26)
  - Wallace Wade Stadium, 1989-1990 (Box 26)
  - Golf Course, fundraising, 1989-1990 (Box 26)
  - Golf Course, 1989-1990 (Box 26)
  - Golf Course/Pro Shop, 1990 (Box 26)
  - Recreation Center, 1990 (Box 26)
  - Iron Dukes, 1990 (Box 26)
  - Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 26)
  - North Carolina Amateur Sports, 1988 Oct.-Nov. (Box 26)
  - NACDA, 1990 (Box 26)
  - Committee on Cost Reductions, 1989-1990 (Box 26)
  - NCAA
    - Division IA Directors of Athletics meeting, 1990 Sept. (Box 26)
    - NCAA, 1990, 3 folders (Box 26)
    - Restructuring Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 26)
    - Convention [Dallas, TX], 1990 Jan. (Box 26)
    - Division I Basketball Committee, 1990 (Box 26)
    - Basketball Committee meeting [Chicago, IL], 1990 Jan.-Feb. (Box 26)
    - Committee on Membership Structure, 1990 Feb. (Box 26)
  - Duke Seminar, 1990 Feb. (Box 26)
  - Wallace Wade/Charles Hipp correspondence, 1939-1940 (Box 26)
  - Athletic Policy Manual of Duke University, 1999 Nov. (Box 26)
- Contracts and Schedules, 1990-1996, 1.5 boxes
  Series contains contracts and agreements between Duke University and other colleges, universities, and academies, travel itineraries, game schedules, and lists of lettering athletes for several revenue and nonrevenue sports.
  For a period of twenty-five years from the origin of the material, permission in writing from the director of the office of origin and the University Archivist is required for use. After twenty-five years, records that have been processed may be consulted with the permission of the University Archivist.
  - 1990-1991, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - 1991-1992, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - 1992-1993, 2 folders (Box 26)
  - 1993-1994, 2 folders (Box 27)
  - 1994-1995, 2 folders (Box 27)
  - 1995-1996, 2 folders (Box 27)
- Accession UA2019-0087, circa 1990s-2007
  Conditions Governing Access
  Access restricted. Collection contains administrative records less than 25 years old. Contact University Archives for access.
  - Trustee Committee on Athletics (Box 28)
  - Awards (Box 28)
  - Public Affairs (Box 28)
  - Promotions (Box 28)
  - Recreational Advisory Committee (Box 28)
  - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 28)
    Restricted: Requires screening for BOT and donor materials.
  - Kenan Institute for Ethics (Box 28)
  - Duke Athletics and the Kenan Institute for Ethics (Box 28)
  - Summer Camps (Box 28)
  - Women's Basketball Sales Report, 1996-1997 (Box 28)
  - Ticket Office Correspondence (Box 28)
  - Training Division (Box 28)
  - Training Room (Box 28)
  - Tallman Trask (Box 28)
  - Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 28)
  - Varsity Club (Box 28)
  - NCAA Championships (Al Buehler), 2000 (Box 28)
  - Wilson Center-Live for Life (Box 28)
  - Wallace Wade Stadium (Box 28)
  - Golf Correspondence, 2001 (Box 28)
  - UNC Report (Box 28)
  - Bowl Correspondence (Box 28)
  - Division IA Athletic Directors' Association (Box 28)
  - Policy (Box 28)
  - HPER (Box 28)
  - TV Rights, 1995 (Box 28)
  - NCHSSA: N. Carolina High School Athletic Association (Box 28)
  - Junior Olympics (Box 28)
  - Correspondence on Recreation Facility Cameron Annex: All Others, 1996 (Box 28)